ktfmissions.com 2012-01-02

# KTFM Privacy Policy - Keep The Faith Missions

**Keep The Faith Missions (KTFM) will adhere to a strict privacy policy.**

To join the KTFM website, you will be required to submit your name, e-mail address, date of birth, along with preferred screen name and password, for verification purposes. 

Any minor child that joins the site must also disclose parent(s) full and/or user name.KFTM will not sell, nor make available your personal information to any third parties. (We may disclose information you give us if required by Federal law, such as the Privacy Act.) 

Please never give personal information on the website. This is including but not limited to address, phone number, and password or Social Security number. It is at your discretion to give any personal information via PM (private message) to another member.

The KTFM website does collect information such as IP addresses used by each member. This is for the benefit of the administrators and/or moderators. IP addresses will not be released to any third parties.KTFM will from time to time send e-mail notices to their members. KTFM may also occasionally send site wide private messages. 

If you wish not to receive these e-mails and/or private messages, you may select not to do so in your user profile.KTFM adheres to the FTC's Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Parent(s) of a minor child may contact us to review the child's account information, and/or have the child's account deleted.

Keep The Faith Missions Administration [ktfmissions@gmail.com](mailto:ktfmissions@gmail.com)

P.O. Box 1019 Reevesville, SC 29471-1019
